We have a buy opinion and we have been consistently giving
buy opinions on insurance companies,
so today we are
giving a buy opinion. The chart of ICICI Lombard General
Insurance has become very strong.
A base has formed at the lower levels. If we
look at the long term chart, a breakout of a Gulls Flag
pattern is also visible on the chart.
So we believe that
you will get a safe return in ICICI Lombard
in the coming time. Buying on a dip at current levels is
quite good. There is a reversal from below. There was a lot of
problem. The stock was also stalled and has a very
strong base. It is moving around 1277.
Now it is highly unlikely that the stock will
go below 1220-1225. There could be a downside maximum of 56. It does
not seem to go much below this. So, on correction on these lines, we have
invested in ICICI Lombard and
our target is 1600. So invest
in ICICI Lombard for the target of 1600.